newsfirst.lk 2011-05-29

# Privacy

**How we may use your information**

We thank you for visiting our web site located at [www.newsfirst.lk](http://www.newsfirst.lk/)  ("Site"), We may use any User Information/data  entered by You or gathered for the following purposes:

1\. market research and to improve the quality of sevice to You by Us; and

 2\. in order to send You periodic communications (this may include e-mail), about features, products and services, events and special offers.

 If you wish that you do not require such communications You may click no communications at all, I would like communications from any party,  I would like communications only from newsfirst. When You enter your User Information, We presume that You accept that your User Information may be retained by Us and that it may be held by Us or any third party company which processes it on behalf of Us. By continuing to use this website and by providing any personal data to Us via this website or e-mail addresses provided on this website, You are consenting to our use of your data for the limited purposes as set in this Privacy Policy. This Policy is devised to help you feel more confident about the privacy and security of your personal details. We process personal data only in strict compliance with accepted privacy norms.

 **Statement**

"You" shall mean you, the user of the Site. "We/Us" means MTV Channel (Pvt) Ltd and any member of the The Capital Maharaja Organization Limited. "Users" means the users of the Site collectively and/or individually as the context allows. 

**Updates**

You may notify Us of any updates, amendments and corrections to previously collected User Information by using the Contact Us section of the Site.We may change this privacy policy from time to time and you should check these regularly. Your use of the Newsfirst Site will be deemed an acceptance of the privacy policy existing at that time. We reserve the right, at any time, to modify, alter, or update this Privacy Policy. 

**Data Collection**

When using the Site You may encounter areas such as games, competitions, chat forums, shopping or video services where You may be asked to enter User Information. Such User Information will only be used for the purposes for which it was collected, for any other purposes specified at the collection point and in accordance with this Privacy Policy.

 **Cookies**

You should be aware that information and data may be automatically collected through the use of Cookies. "Cookies" are small text files that store basic information that a web site can use to recognise repeat site visits and as an example, recall your name if this has been previously supplied. We may use this to observe behaviour and compile aggregate data in order to improve the Site, target the advertising and assess general effectiveness of such advertising. 

**Disclaimer of Liability**

Newsfirst presents the information on this Site as a service to the community and other internet users. In case the User intends to cite information that contain in this Site; the User shall cite the name Newsfirst. While the information on this Site is about news items and issues, it is not strict advice for the public. Moreover, due to any interruption, miss- transmission or any other technical difficulty, We make no warranty or guarantee concerning the accuracy or reliability of the content at this Site or at other sites to which We link. 

**Contact**

Any queries or comments about this policy should be forwarded to:  

This e-mail address is being protected from spambots. You need JavaScript enabled to view it.   
Any site that you may connect to from here is not covered by this Privacy Policy.
